{
    "id": "6c9fa3fc812849708a791804987bbed2",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise (Intermediate Level)",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I …..................... . yesterday.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "went for a walk",
                "went for walk",
                "had been going for a walk"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "34b0f827b397452a909a934f2ef302ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "He got angry before I ..................... .. a word.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "said",
                "had said",
                "have said"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "19e9e9024ee344e3aeab75445c07dcad"
        },
        {
            "question": "If I ...................... this I shall be wrong.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "did",
                "will do"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "913ea158a2e249139c6ccf7a22a32921"
        },
        {
            "question": "He said that he ………………… him the day before.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "saw",
                "had seen",
                "was seeing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bffef6fba4f24df6bd480f3643544a91"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rita asked ………………….. she could go home.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "weather",
                "whether"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "28b4da42e9cd465ba8d9028c36115653"
        },
        {
            "question": "When I ………………… to Mumbai I will see him.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "went",
                "had gone"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "778491082ac14cddb994661ed918d048"
        },
        {
            "question": "He ..................... smoking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has left",
                "has given up"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9871e4fa34ff4901bcd69b619163c556"
        },
        {
            "question": "We …………………. playing when it started raining.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "left",
                "stopped"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2e816e5c778546d3a7be6e2de50696bb"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went to America to ……………… English.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "learn",
                "know"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fcc8a0c823e443199ad7339f4016b2d4"
        },
        {
            "question": "She knows …………………..",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to swim",
                "how to swim"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "839b324ff1174d4fbc320c5e54d48e11"
        }
    ]
}